Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- S
  - X346 S27, 1949 - 1984; nos. 1-316, 267 catalogs
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1632, Folder 10304-10308)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1633, Folder 10309-10313)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1634, Folder 10314-10318)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1635, Folder 10319-10324)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1636, Folder 10325-10329)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1637, Folder 10330-10335)
    - Chas. J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1638, Folder 10336)
  - X346 S27 I, 1951 - 1961; nos. 6-14, 9 catalogs
    - Chas J. Sawyer, LTD; London (Box 1638, Folder 10337)
  - X346 S281, undated; no. 11, 1 catalog
    - Scala Autographs; Coral Gables, Florida (Box 1638, Folder 10338)
  - X346 S289, [1940-ca. 1989]; nos. 1-79, 76 catalogs
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1638, Folder 10339-10342)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1639, Folder 10343-10348)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1640, Folder 10349-10354)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1641, Folder 10355-10360)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1642, Folder 10361-10366)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1643, Folder 10367-10372)
    - William H. Schab; New York, N.Y. (Box 1644, Folder 10373-10378)
  - X346 S294, [ca. 1941-ca. 1944]; nos. 1-7, 7 catalogs
    - Marie E. Schaefer; Pasadena, California (Box 1645, Folder 10379)
  - X346 S309, [ca. 1971-1986]; nos. 3-30, 27 catalogs
    - Jörg Schäfer; Zurich (Box 1645, Folder 10380-10384)
    - Jörg Schäfer; Zurich (Box 1646, Folder 10385-10386)
  - X346 S312, undated, [1972]; nos. 1-14, 3 catalogs
    - Walter Schatzki; New York, N.Y. (Box 1646, Folder 10387)
  - X346 S323, 1904-[ca. 1947]; nos. 27-128, 38 catalogs
    Includes catalogs from the new series
    - Librairie Jean Schemit; Paris (Box 1646, Folder 10388-10394)
    - Librairie Jean Schemit; Paris (Box 1647, Folder 10395)
  - X346 S33, [1973-1985]; nos. 16-44, 6 catalogs
    - Justin G. Schiller; New York, N.Y. (Box 1647, Folder 10396)
  - X346 S345, undated; nos. 65-91, 17 catalogs
    - Schmorl, Seefeld, Nachf; Hannover (Box 1647, Folder 10397-10398)
  - X346 S35, undated; nos. 3-18, 8 catalogs
    - Annemarie Schnase; Scarsdale, N. Y. (Box 1647, Folder 10399-10400)
  - X346 S36, 1978; no. 317, 1 list
    - Schneemann Books; Chicago, IL (Box 1648, Folder 10401)
  - X346 S366, [1908]; no. 95, 1 catalog
    - Ferdinand Schöningh; Osnabrück (Box 1648, Folder 10402)
  - X346 S374, [1972-1986]; nos. 2-17, 8 catalogs
    - E. K. Schreiber; New York (Box 1648, Folder 10403-10404)
  - X346 S3868, [1906]-1912; nos. 7-51, unnumbered, 19 catalogs
    - Theo E. Schulte; New York City (Box 1648, Folder 10405-10406)
  - X346 S387, undated, 1914-1966; unnumbered, nos. 56-329, 210 catalogs
    - Schulte's Bookstore, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1648, Folder 10407-10410)
    - Schulte's Bookstore, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1649, Folder 10411-10416)
    - Schulte's Bookstore, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1650, Folder 10417-10422)
    - Schulte's Bookstore, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1651, Folder 10423-10428)
    - Schulte's Bookstore, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1652, Folder 10429-10433)
  - X346 S3992, undated, 1939; unnumbered, nos. 36-39, 6 catalogs
    - J. Schwartz; New York, N. Y. (Box 1653, Folder 10434)
  - X346 S416, 1951 - 1953; nos. 18-24, 3 catalogs
    - Scientific Book Supply Service; London (Box 1653, Folder 10435)
  - X346 S417, 1951 - 1977; nos. 10-80, 52 catalogs
    - Scientific Library Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 1653, Folder 10436-10439)
    - Scientific Library Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 1654, Folder 10440-10444)
    - Scientific Library Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 1655, Folder 10445-10447)
  - X346 S4175, 1972; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John Scopazzi; San Francisco, Calif. (Box 1655, Folder 10448)
  - X346 S429, 1969; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - B.J. Scott; Winthrop Harbor, Illinois (Box 1655, Folder 10449)
  - X346 S43, 1811 - 1817; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - John Simco; London (Box 1655, Folder 10450)
  - X346 S434, 1869 - 1914; unnumbered, 32 catalogs
    Name variant: Charles Scribner's Sons
    - Scribner, Welford Co.; New York (Box 1655, Folder 10451-10452)
    - Scribner, Welford Co.; New York (Box 1656, Folder 10453-10458)
    - Scribner, Welford Co.; New York (Box 1657, Folder 10459)
  - X346 S434 I, 1895-[ca. 1968]; nos. 34-174, 109 catalogs
    Name variants: Scribner's; Scribner Bookstore
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1657, Folder 10460-10464)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1658, Folder 10465-10470)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1659, Folder 10471-10476)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1660, Folder 10477-10482)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1661, Folder 10483-10489)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons; New York (Box 1662, Folder 10490-10494)
  - X346 S434 II, 1939 - 1955; nos. 1-21, unnumbered, 21 bulletins
    - Scribner Book Store; New York City (Box 1663, Folder 10495)
  - X346 S434 III, [1960s-1972]; nos. 1-55, 17 lists
    - Scribner Book Store; New York, New York (Box 1663, Folder 10496)
  - X346 S434 IV, [ca. 1909-ca. 1951]; unnumbered, 22 catalogs
    - Scribner Bookstore; New York (Box 1663, Folder 10497-10501)
  - X346 S437, [1972]-1976; nos. 1-5, 6 catalogs
    - Scriptorium; Beverly Hills, Ca. (Box 1664, Folder 10502)
  - X346 S439, 1921 - 1931; nos. 22-34, 10 catalogs
    - Townley Searle; London (Box 1664, Folder 10503)
  - X346 S445, 1945 - 1946; nos. 1-9, 7 catalogs
    - Ralph C. Secord; Hartford, Conn. (Box 1664, Folder 10504)
  - X346 S465, [1968-1986]; nos. 18-44, 5 catalogs
    - Serendipity Books; Berkeley, Ca. (Box 1664, Folder 10505-10506)
  - X346 S49, 1822; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Sams; London (Box 1664, Folder 10507)
  - X346 S496, 1946 - 1976; nos. 22-37, 16 catalogs
    - Seven Gables Bookshop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1664, Folder 10508)
    - Seven Gables Bookshop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1665, Folder 10509-10511)
  - X346 S496 II, [ca. 1954]-1957; nos. 3-7, unnumbered, 5 lists
    - Seven Gables Bookshop; New York, N.Y. (Box 1665, Folder 10512)
  - X346 S518, 1922-1956, undated; nos. 4-57, 53 catalogs
    Name variant: George Sexton (Books) Ltd. Location variant: Sussex, England
    - G. Sexton; Bexhill-On-Sea, England (Box 1665, Folder 10513-10514)
    - G. Sexton; Bexhill-On-Sea, England (Box 1666, Folder 10515-10519)
  - X346 S52, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - San Francisco Art Gallery; San Francisco, California (Box 1666, Folder 10520)
  - X346 S527, 1970; no. 281, 1 catalog
    - Chas. J. Sawyer; London (Box 1666, Folder 10521)
  - X346 S55, 1938; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John D. Sherman, Jr.; Mount Vernon, New York (Box 1667, Folder 10522)
  - X346 S55 I, 1917 - 1956; nos. 4-69, 62 catalogs
    - John D. Sherman, Jr.; Mount Vernon, New York (Box 1667, Folder 10523-10527)
    - John D. Sherman, Jr.; Mount Vernon, New York (Box 1668, Folder 10528-10533)
    - John D. Sherman, Jr.; Mount Vernon, New York (Box 1669, Folder 10534-10539)
  - X346 S554, undated, 1911-1918; nos. 2-111, 5 catalogs
    - The Sherwood Company; New York City (Box 1669, Folder 10540)
  - X346 S563, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Sibrium Libri e. Manoscritti; Milano (Box 1670, Folder 10541)
  - X346 S565, undated; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - Sanders of Oxford Ltd.; Oxford (Box 1670, Folder 10542)
  - X346 S565 I, 1961 - 1963; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Sanders of Oxford Ltd.; Oxford (Box 1670, Folder 10543)
  - X346 S565 II, undated; unnumbered, 13 catalogs
    - Sanders of Oxford Ltd.; Oxford (Box 1670, Folder 10544-10545)
  - X346 S565 III, undated, 1953-1954, undated; nos. 2-4, unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Sanders and Co.; Oxford (Box 1670, Folder 10546-10547)
  - X346 S565 IV, [1926-1985]; nos. 1-109, 39 catalogs
    - Sanders Co.; Oxford (Box 1671, Folder 10548-10553)
  - X346 S572, undated; no. 26, 1 list
    - Signal Books; Harrisonburg, Virginia (Box 1672, Folder 10554)
  - X346 S579, 1938 - 1944; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Siler's Book Store; New Orleans (Box 1672, Folder 10555)
  - X346 S589, 1872-[ca. 1938]; nos. 12-279, 118 catalogs
    - Simmel Co.; Leipzig (Box 1672, Folder 10556-10561)
    - Simmel Co.; Leipzig (Box 1673, Folder 10562-10572)
    - Simmel Co.; Leipzig (Box 1674, Folder 10573-10582)
    - Simmel Co.; Leipzig (Box 1675, Folder 10583-10588)
    - Simmel Co.; Leipzig (Box 1676, Folder 10589-10590)
  - X346 S594, 1908 - 1958; nos. 217-415, 101 catalogs
    Includes two bulletins from another series
    - Simmons Waters; Leamington Spa, Warwickshire (Box 1676, Folder 10591-10594)
    - Simmons Waters; Leamington Spa, Warwickshire (Box 1677, Folder 10595-10599)
  - X346 S611, [1942]; no. 76, 1 list
    - M.C. Simons; New York City (Box 1677, Folder 10600)
  - X346 S612, 1927 - 1969; nos. 10-342, 123 catalogs
    Name variant: Librairie Simonson
    - Raoul Simonson; Bruxelles (Box 1677, Folder 10601-10603)
    - Raoul Simonson; Bruxelles (Box 1678, Folder 10604-10609)
    - Raoul Simonson; Bruxelles (Box 1679, Folder 10610-10613)
  - X346 S615, 1949-[1986]; nos. 11-107, 105 catalogs
    - George Frederick Sims; Harrow, Middlesex (Box 1679, Folder 10614-10615)
    - George Frederick Sims; Harrow, Middlesex (Box 1680, Folder 10616-10621)
    - George Frederick Sims; Harrow, Middlesex (Box 1681, Folder 10622-10624)
  - X346 S631, [ca. 1926]-1979; nos. 17-315, 105 catalogs
    Name variant: Librairie M. Slatkine & Fils
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1681, Folder 10625-10627)
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1682, Folder 10628-10637)
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1683, Folder 10638-10643)
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1684, Folder 10644-10651)
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1685, Folder 10652-10657)
    - Librairie M. Slatkine; Geneve (Box 1686, Folder 10658-10662)
  - X346 S6423, 1841 - 1905; various numberings, 75 catalogs
    Includes several series. Name variant: John Russell Smith
    - Alfred Russell Smith; London (Box 1686, Folder 10663-10664)
    - Alfred Russell Smith; London (Box 1687, Folder 10665-10671)
    - Alfred Russell Smith; London (Box 1688, Folder 10672-10677)
    - Alfred Russell Smith; London (Box 1689, Folder 10678-10682)
    - Alfred Russell Smith; London (Box 1690, Folder 10683)
  - X346 S648, undated, 1896-[1912]; nos. 1-173, 15 catalogs
    - Geo. D. Smith; New York (Box 1690, Folder 10684-10686)
  - X346 S648 I, 1896-[1916], undated; unnumbered, 60 catalogs
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1691, Folder 10687-10692)
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1692, Folder 10693-10697)
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1693, Folder 10698-10699)
  - X346 S648 II, 1914, undated; unnumbered, nos. 101-121, unnumbered, 23 catalogs
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1693, Folder 10700-19703)
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1694, Folder 10704-10705)
  - X346 S648 III, undated; nos. 5-7, 3 catalogs
    - George D. Smith; New York (Box 1694, Folder 10706)
  - X346 S648 IV, undated; no. 9, 1 bulletin
    - Geo. D. Smith; New York (Box 1694, Folder 10707)
  - X346 S652, 1921 - 1976; nos. 1-53, 54 catalogs
    Includes supplements and lists
    - John Smith Son (Glasgow) Ltd.; Glascow (Box 1694, Folder 10708-10711)
    - John Smith Son (Glasgow) Ltd.; Glascow (Box 1695, Folder 10712-10717)
    - John Smith Son (Glasgow) Ltd.; Glascow (Box 1696, Folder 10718-10723)
    - John Smith Son (Glasgow) Ltd.; Glascow (Box 1697, Folder 10724-10728)
  - X346 S662, undated; nos. 1-45, 37 catalogs
    Name variant: Stanley Smith & Keith Fawkes
    - Stanley Smith, The Marchmont Bookshop; London (Box 1697, Folder 10729)
    - Stanley Smith, The Marchmont Bookshop; London (Box 1698, Folder 10730-10733)
  - X346 S663, undated; no. 9, 1 catalog
    - Sydney R. Smith; Canaan, N. Y. (Box 1698, Folder 10734)
  - X346 S664 II, 1904 - 1981; nos. 1-209, 150 catalogs
    Name variants: William Smith & Son; William Smith (Booksellers) Ltd. Includes supplements
    - William Smith; Reading (Box 1698, Folder 10735-10738)
    - William Smith; Reading (Box 1699, Folder 10739-10744)
    - William Smith; Reading (Box 1700, Folder 10745-10750)
    - William Smith; Reading (Box 1701, Folder 10751-10757)
    - William Smith; Reading (Box 1702, Folder 10758-10760)
  - X346 S6644, 1913 - 1974; nos. 10-194, 22 catalogs
    - William H. Smith, Jr.; Norwalk, Conn. (Box 1702, Folder 10761-10763)
  - X346 S665, undated, 1932-1940, undated; nos. 1-354, 216 catalogs
    Location variant: Fort Thomas, KY. Includes lists
    - The Smith Book Co.; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 1703, Folder 10764-10769)
    - The Smith Book Co.; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 1704, Folder 10770-10776)
    - The Smith Book Co.; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 1705, Folder 10777)
  - X346 S665 I, undated; nos. 1-123, 36 lists
    - The Smith Book Co.; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 1705, Folder 10778-10779)
  - X346 S667, 1925 - 1932; nos. 6-13, 8 catalogs
    - W. R. Smyth; Rathgar, Dublin (Box 1705, Folder 10780)
  - X346 S667 I, 1944 - 1951; nos. 1-11, 6 lists
    - W. R. Smyth; Rathgar, Dublin (Box 1705, Folder 10781)
  - X346 S667 II, 1947; unnumbered, 1 list
    - W. R. Smyth; Rathgar, Dublin (Box 1705, Folder 10782)
  - X346 S67, 1948-1952, undated; nos. 1-177, 66 catalogs
    - The Social Science Book Store; New York, N. Y. (Box 1705, Folder 10783-10785)
    - The Social Science Book Store; New York, N. Y. (Box 1706, Folder 10786-10791)
    - The Social Science Book Store; New York, N. Y. (Box 1707, Folder 10792-10797)
    - The Social Science Book Store; New York, N. Y. (Box 1708, Folder 10798)
  - X346 S67 II, undated; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - The Social Science Book Store; New York, N. Y. (Box 1708, Folder 10799)
  - X346 S684, 1895 - 1896; nos. 3-7, 6 catalogs
    - Leonard C. Smithers; London (Box 1708, Folder 10800-10801)
  - X346 S69, 1972; no. 2, 1 catalog
    - Somerville Rare Books Ltd.; Dublin, Ireland (Box 1708, Folder 10802)
  - X346 S71, 1862 - 1888; unnumbered, nos. 32-187, unnumbered, 86 catalogs
    Name variants: H. Sotheran, J. Baer & Co.; Henry Sotheran & Co. Includes duplicates
    - Willis and Sotheran; London (Box 1708, Folder 10803)
    - Willis and Sotheran; London (Box 1709, Folder 10804-10807)
    - Willis and Sotheran; London (Box 1710, Folder 10808-10813)
    - Willis and Sotheran; London (Box 1711, Folder 10814-10817)
  - X346 S71 I, 1868-1985, undated; nos. [244]-996, 543 catalogs
    Name variants: H. Sotheran, J. Baer & Co.; Henry Sotheran, Ltd. Includes duplicates and lists
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1712, Folder 10818-10823)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1713, Folder 10824-10829)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1714, Folder 10830-10835)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1715, Folder 10836-10841)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1716, Folder 10842-10847)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1717, Folder 10848-10853)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1718, Folder 10854-10859)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1719, Folder 10860-10865)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1720, Folder 10866-10871)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1721, Folder 10872-10877)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1722, Folder 10878-10884)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1723, Folder 10885-10890)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1724, Folder 10891-10896)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1725, Folder 10897-10902)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1726, Folder 10903-10908)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1727, Folder 10909-10913)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1728, Folder 10914-10919)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1729, Folder 10920-10925)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1730, Folder 10926-10931)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1731, Folder 10932-10937)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1732, Folder 10938-10943)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1733, Folder 10944-10949)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1734, Folder 10950-10955)
  - X346 S71 II, 1891-1919, undated; nos. 1-98, 65 catalogs
    Name variant: Henry Sotheran & Co.
    - H. Southeran Co.; London (Box 1735, Folder 10956-10961)
    - H. Southeran Co.; London (Box 1736, Folder 10962-10967)
    - H. Southeran Co.; London (Box 1737, Folder 10968-10973)
    - H. Southeran Co.; London (Box 1738, Folder 10974-10977)
  - X346 S71 III, 1889 - 1893; nos. 77-108, 10 catalogs
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; Manchester (Box 1738, Folder 10978-10980)
  - X346 S71 IV, 1871-1911, undated; unnumbered, 24 catalogs
    Name variant: Henry Sotheran, Ltd. Includes lists
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1739, Folder 10981-10987)
    - Henry Sotheran Co.; London (Box 1740, Folder 10988-10991)
  - X346 S71 V, 1933 - 1938; nos. 1-23, 25 catalogs
    Includes two catalogs from other series'
    - Henry Sotheran, Ltd.; London (Box 1740, Folder 10992-10994)
    - Henry Sotheran, Ltd.; London (Box 1741, Folder 10995-11000)
  - X346 S71 VIII, 1936 - 1937; nos. 1-6, 6 catalogs
    - Henry Sotheran, Ltd.; London (Box 1742, Folder 11001-11002)
  - X346 S722, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Southern Appalachian Rare Book Co.; Whittier, North Carolina (Box 1742, Folder 11003)
  - X346 S725, 1938-1941, undated; nos. 4-30, 12 lists; nos. 30-195, 149 catalogs
    - Southern Book Co.; Baltimore, Md. (Box 1742, Folder 11004-11008)
    - Southern Book Co.; Baltimore, Md. (Box 1743, Folder 11009-11014)
    - Southern Book Co.; Baltimore, Md. (Box 1744, Folder 11015-11020)
    - Southern Book Co.; Baltimore, Md. (Box 1745, Folder 11021--11022)
  - X346 S725 I, undated, 1940-1943; unnumbered, 19 lists
    - Southern Book Co.; Baltimore, Md. (Box 1745, Folder 11023-11024)
  - X346 S7275, 1938 - 1952; nos. 1-7, 7 catalogs; nos. 8-157, 52 lists
    Location variants: New Braunfels, Texas; New Orleans, Louisiana.
    - The Southern Library Service; Hattiesburg, Mississippi (Box 1745, Folder 11025-11027)
    - The Southern Library Service; Hattiesburg, Mississippi (Box 1746, Folder 11028-11031)
  - X346 S7275 I, 1945-1946, undated; nos. 1-12, unnumbered, 14 lists
    Location variant: Biloxi, Mississippi. Includes a duplicate
    - The Southern Library Service; Hattiesburg, Mississippi (Box 1746, Folder 11032-11033)
    - The Southern Library Service; Hattiesburg, Mississippi (Box 1747, Folder 11034)
  - X346 S7275 II, 1940 - 1941; nos. 17-21, 3 special lists
    - The Southern Library Service; Hattiesburg, Mississippi (Box 1747, Folder 11035)
  - X346 S731, undated; nos. 1-79, unnumbered, 65 catalogs
    Name variant: Roy Vernon Sowers. Some catalog numbers in more than one part
    - Roy V. Sowers; Pasadena California (Box 1747, Folder 11036-11042)
    - Roy V. Sowers; Pasadena California (Box 1748, Folder 11043-11047)
  - X346 S732, undated; nos. 67-81, 3 catalogs
    - August Späth; München (Box 1748, Folder 11048)
  - X346 S732 II, undated; nos. 42-75, 2 lists
    - August Späth; München (Box 1748, Folder 11049)
  - X346 S733, undated; nos. 1-194, 11 catalogs
    Name variant: D. R. Spaight, Bookseller. Location variants: Waterford, Virginia; Tall Timbers, Maryland
    - D. R. Spaight Rare Books; New Orleans, La. (Box 1748, Folder 11050)
    - D. R. Spaight Rare Books; New Orleans, La. (Box 1749, Folder 11051)
  - X346 S759, 1891-1902, undated; nos. 1-94, 54 catalogs
    - M. Spirgatis; Leipzig (Box 1749, Folder 11052-11057)
    - M. Spirgatis; Leipzig (Box 1750, Folder 11058-11063)
  - X346 S776, undated; nos. 5-30, 23 catalogs
    Name variant: F. & G. Staack. Location variant: Camden, Maine
    - Staack; New York City (Box 1750, Folder 11064)
    - Staack; New York City (Box 1751, Folder 11065-11069)
  - X346 S783, 1915 - 1941; nos. 1-20, 13 catalogs
    - P. Stammer Bookseller and Bookhunter; New York City (Box 1752, Folder 11070-11071)
  - X346 S783 II, 1939-1944, undated; nos. 1-235, 28 catalogs
    - P. Stammer Bookseller and Bookhunter; New York City (Box 1752, Folder 11072-11075)
  - X346 S783 III, undated; no. 12, 1 list
    - Stammer's Bookstore; N. Y. C. (Box 1752, Folder 11076)
  - X346 S784, undated; nos. 109-239, 120 catalogs
    Name variant: Antiquariaat H. K. Overdiep
    - N. V. Standaard-Boekhandel; Antwerpen (Box 1753, Folder 11077-11082)
    - N. V. Standaard-Boekhandel; Antwerpen (Box 1754, Folder 11083-11087)
  - X346 S784 II, undated; nos. 2-3, 2 catalogs
    - N. V. Standaard-Boekhandel; Antwerpen (Box 1754, Folder 11088)
  - X346 S784 III, undated; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - N. V. Standaard-Boekhandel; Antwerpen (Box 1754, Folder 11089)
  - X346 S794, 1860 - 1968; nos. 7-586, 133 catalogs
    Location variant: Marburg
    - J. A. Stargardt; Berlin (Box 1755, Folder 11090-11103)
    - J. A. Stargardt; Berlin (Box 1756, Folder 11104-11115)
    - J. A. Stargardt; Berlin (Box 1757, Folder 11116-11128)
    - J. A. Stargardt; Berlin (Box 1758, Folder 11129-11134)
  - X346 S795, 1875 - 1883; nos. 105-138, 18 catalogs
    - John Mozley Stark; London (Box 1758, Folder 11135-11136)
    - John Mozley Stark; London (Box 1759, Folder 11137-11138)
  - X346 S7955, [1961-1963]; nos. 101-145, 18 catalogs
    - Starr Book Shop; Cambridge, Mass. (Box 1759, Folder 11139-11140)
  - X346 S811, 1918 - 1954; various numberings, 10 lists
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1759, Folder 11141-11142)
  - X346 S811 II, 1920 - 1969; nos. 1-383, 293 catalogs
    Name variant: Stechert-Hafner, Inc. Includes seven lists from a separate series
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1759, Folder 11143-11144)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1760, Folder 11145-11152)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1761, Folder 11153-11158)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1762, Folder 11159-11164)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1763, Folder 11165-11170)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1764, Folder 11171-11176)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1765, Folder 11177-11182)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1766, Folder 11183-11188)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1767, Folder 11189-11194)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1768, Folder 11195-11200)
    - G.E. Stechert Co.; New York (Box 1769, Folder 11201-11205)
  - X346 S813, 1909 - 1976; nos. 13-130, 101 catalogs
    - Robert D. Steedman; Newcastle-on-Tyne (Box 1769, Folder 11206-11207)
    - Robert D. Steedman; Newcastle-on-Tyne (Box 1770, Folder 11208-11213)
    - Robert D. Steedman; Newcastle-on-Tyne (Box 1771, Folder 11214-11219)
  - X346 S814, undated; nos. 13-24, 9 catalogs
    - Geoffrey Steele; Chappaqua, New York (Box 1771, Folder 11220)
  - X346 S8165, [1966]-1977; nos. 208-310, 17 catalogs
    - Antiquariat Stenderhoff; Münster (Box 1772, Folder 11221-11225)
  - X346 S8188, 1914 - 1987; nos. 1-29, 34 catalogs
    Includes catalogs from several series
    - B.F. Stevens Brown Ltd.; London, England (Box 1772, Folder 11226-11228)
    - B.F. Stevens Brown Ltd.; London, England (Box 1773, Folder 11229-11231)
  - X346 S82, 1885-[1916]; nos. 4-94, 77 catalogs
    Name variant: Henry Stevens, Son and Stiles
    - Henry Stevens Son; London (Box 1773, Folder 11232-11234)
    - Henry Stevens Son; London (Box 1774, Folder 11235-11239)
  - X346 S82 I, 1907 - 1966; nos. 1-35, 36 catalogs
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1774, Folder 11240-11241)
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1775, Folder 11242-11245)
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1776, Folder 11246-11249)
  - X346 S82 III, 1928 - 1984; nos. 1-98, 85 catalogs
    Includes duplicates and two miscellaneous catalogs.
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1776, Folder 11250-11251)
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1777, Folder 11252-11257)
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1778, Folder 11258-11263)
    - Henry Stevens Son and Stiles; London (Box 1779, Folder 11264-11266)